



Core Competencies

- · Graphic Designing
- · Logo Design
- Brochure Design
- Illustrator
- Indesign
- Photoshop
- Branding
- · Digital Marketing
- Advertising
- · Campaign design
- digital illustration
- · Proposal Design
- Pursuit Design
- Infographics
- Analyst Graphic Designer
- Graphic Designer
- Presentation Design



Technical Skills

- ILLUSTRATOR
- PHOTOSHOP
- INDESIGN
- MS OFFICE
- CANVA



Personal Information

Date of birth 04-Nov-1997

Sweta Kabi

Analyst Graphic Designer



2 years 10 months



9113478360



sweta4kabi@gmail.com



Associate Graphic Designer seeking roles in Graphic Designing, Logo Design,Brochure Design,Branding,Digital Marketing, Advertising,Campaign design,digital illustration,Proposal Design, Pursuit Design,Infographics,Illustrator,Indesign,Photoshop, Presentation design, Newsletters design, Article design, Social Media creative.



Profile Summary

A result oriented professional with over 2.9 years of experience in Graphic Designing,Logo Design,Brochure Design,Branding,Digital
Marketing,Advertising,Campaign design,digital
illustration,Proposal Design,Pursuit
Design,Infographics,Illustrator,Indesign,Photoshop, BFA
Graduated, Professional Painter / Artist. Currently
working in KNAV experience in this field through Deloitte,
ICAT and writerdesk as Graphic Designer. Also interned in
Abhishek graphics vododra. I have knowledge and
experience in the field of event management and
organising art exhibition. Honestly, I have all the skills and
experience that you're looking for. If given me chance, I would like
to work dedicatedly.



Education

BFA, 2020

Sri Sri University



Work Experience

March 2023

Associate Graphic Designer

KNAV

Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

Analyst Graphic Designer

Deloitte

Gender Female

Address

New Subhash Colony Road No 3a Dimna Road Mango Jamshedpur, Jharkhand

City Bangalore/Bengaluru

Country INDIA

Jun 2021 - Mar 2022

Graphic Designer

ICAT Media and Design Collage

Jun 2020 - May 2021

Graphic Designer

Writerdesk